They had their turn... now it's his
The Liability is a thriller, comedy, crime film directed by Craig Viveiros.
When 19-year-old Adam agrees to do a day's driving for his mum's gangster boyfriend Peter, it takes him on a 24-hour
journey into a nightmarish world of murder, sex trafficking and revenge, in the company of aging hit man Roy.
Roy, played by Tim Roth.
Adam, played by Jack O'Connell.
The Girl, played by Talulah Riley.
Nicky, played by Kierston Wareing.
Peter, played by Peter Mullan.
Ivan, played by Christopher Hatherall.
Secondary liability, or indirect infringement, arises when a party materially contributes to, facilitates,
induces, or is otherwise responsible for directly infringing acts carried out by another party.
The US has statutorily codified secondary liability rules for trademarks and patents, but for
matters relating to copyright, this has solely been a product of case law developments.
In other words, courts, rather than Congress, have been the primary
developers of theories and policies concerning secondary liability.
The film explores themes of hitman, road trip, revenge, sex trafficking.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.